Guide to the Language Resource Center collection, circa 1963-1983.
Language Resource Center collection,
- Reel-to-reel tape recordings
  - Unknown
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-14980; FSI (Box 71)
      LRC #: BU 2
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-14981; FSI (Box 71)
      LRC #: BU 3
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-14982; FSI (Box 71)
      LRC #: BU 4
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-14983; FSI (Box 71)
      LRC #: BU 5
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-14984; FSI (Box 71)
      LRC #: BU 6.1
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-14985; FSI (Box 71)
      LRC #: BU 6.2
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-14986; FSI (Box 71)
      LRC #: BU 7.1
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-14987; FSI (Box 71)
      LRC #: BU 7.2
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-14988; FSI (Box 71)
      LRC #: BU 8.1
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-14989; FSI (Box 71)
      LRC #: BU 8.2
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-14990; FSI (Box 71)
      LRC #: BU 9.1
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-14991; FSI (Box 71)
      LRC #: BU 9.2
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-14992; FSI (Box 71)
      LRC #: BU 9.3
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-14993; FSI (Box 71)
      LRC #: BU 10
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-14994; FSI (Box 71)
      LRC #: BU 11
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-14995; FSI (Box 71)
      LRC #: BU 12
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-14996; FSI (Box 71)
      LRC #: BU 13
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-14997; FSI (Box 71)
      LRC #: BU 14
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-14998; FSI (Box 71)
      LRC #: BU 15
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-14999; FSI (Box 71)
      LRC #: BU 16
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-15000; FSI (Box 71)
      LRC #: BU 17
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-15001; FSI (Box 71)
      LRC #: BU 18
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-15002; FSI (Box 71)
      LRC #: BU 19
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-15003; FSI (Box 71)
      LRC #: BU 20
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-15004; FSI (Box 72)
      LRC #: BU 21
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-15005; FSI (Box 72)
      LRC #: BU 22
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-15006; FSI (Box 72)
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-15007; FSI (Box 72)
      LRC #: BU 23
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-15008; FSI (Box 72)
      LRC #: BU 24
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-15009; FSI (Box 72)
      LRC #: BU 25
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-15010; FSI (Box 72)
      LRC #: BU 26
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-15011; FSI (Box 72)
      LRC #: BU 27
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-15012; FSI (Box 72)
      LRC #: BU 28
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-15013; FSI (Box 72)
      LRC #: BU 29
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-15014; FSI (Box 72)
      LRC #: BU 30
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-15015; FSI (Box 72)
      LRC #: BU 31
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-15016; FSI (Box 72)
      LRC #: BU 32
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-15017; FSI (Box 72)
      LRC #: BU 33
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-15018; FSI (Box 72)
      LRC #: BU 34
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-15019; FSI (Box 72)
      LRC #: BU 35
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-15020; FSI (Box 72)
      LRC #: BU 36-39
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-15021; FSI (Box 72)
      LRC #: BU 40
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-15022; FSI (Box 72)
      LRC #: BU 41-44
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-15023; FSI (Box 72)
      LRC #: BU 51-54
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-15024; FSI (Box 72)
      LRC #: BU 55
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-15025; FSI (Box 72)
      LRC #: BU 56-59.1
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-15026; FSI (Box 72)
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-15027; FSI (Box 72)
      LRC #: BU 56-59.2
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-15028; FSI (Box 72)
      LRC #: BU 60
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-15029; FSI (Box 72)
      LRC #: BU 61-65
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-15030; FSI (Box 72)
      LRC #: BU 66-70
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-15031; FSI (Box 72)
      LRC #: BU 71-75
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-15032; FSI (Box 72)
      LRC #: BU 71-74
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-15033; FSI (Box 72)
      LRC #: BU 74-75
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-15034; FSI (Box 72)
      LRC #: BU 76-79
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-15035; FSI (Box 72)
      LRC #: BU 79-80
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-15036; FSI (Box 72)
      LRC #: BU 81-84
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-15037; FSI (Box 72)
      LRC #: BU 84-85
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-15038; FSI (Box 72)
      LRC #: BU 86-89
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-15039; FSI (Box 72)
      LRC #: BU 89-90
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-15040; FSI (Box 72)
      LRC #: BU 91-94
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-15041; FSI (Box 72)
      LRC #: BU 94-95
    - Burmese, Undated; TR-15042; FSI (Box 72)
      LRC #: BU 96-99
    - Hungarian Reading Drills, Undated; TR-15043 (Box 73)
      LRC #: HGRD 1-6
    - Hungarian Reading Drills, Undated; TR-15044 (Box 73)
      LRC #: HGRD 7-14
    - Hungarian Reading Drills, Undated; TR-15045 (Box 73)
      LRC #: HGRD 15-22
    - Hungarian Reading Drills, Undated; TR-15046 (Box 73)
      LRC #: HGRD 23-28
    - Hungarian Reading Drills, Undated; TR-15047 (Box 73)
      LRC #: HGRD 29-33
    - Hungarian Reading Drills, Undated; TR-15048 (Box 73)
      LRC #: HGRD 34-36
    - Hungarian Spelling Drills, Undated; TR-15049 (Box 73)
      LRC #: HGSD 1A
    - Hungarian Spelling Drills, Undated; TR-15050 (Box 73)
      LRC #: HGSD 1B
    - Hungarian Spelling Drills, Undated; TR-15051 (Box 73)
      LRC #: HGSD 2A
    - Hungarian Spelling Drills, Undated; TR-15052 (Box 73)
      LRC #: HGSD 2B
    - Hungarian Spelling Drills, Undated; TR-15053 (Box 73)
      LRC #: HGSD 3A
    - Hungarian Spelling Drills, Undated; TR-15054 (Box 73)
      LRC #: HGSD 3B
    - Hungarian Spelling Drills, Undated; TR-15055 (Box 73)
      LRC #: HGSD 4A
    - Hungarian Spelling Drills, Undated; TR-15056 (Box 73)
      LRC #: HGSD 5A
    - Hungarian Spelling Drills, Undated; TR-15057 (Box 73)
      LRC #: HGSD 5B
    - Hungarian Spelling Drills, Undated; TR-15058 (Box 73)
      LRC #: HGSD 6A
    - Hungarian Spelling Drills, Undated; TR-15059 (Box 73)
      LRC #: HGSD 6B
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-15060; FSI (Box 73)
      LRC #: HG 13.2
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-15061; FSI (Box 73)
      LRC #: HG 13.3
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-15062; FSI (Box 73)
      LRC #: HG 14.1
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-15063; FSI (Box 73)
      LRC #: HG 14.2
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-15064; FSI (Box 73)
      LRC #: HG 14.3
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-15065; FSI (Box 73)
      LRC #: HG 14.4
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-15066; FSI (Box 73)
      LRC #: HG 15.1
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-15067; FSI (Box 73)
      LRC #: HG 15.2
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-15068; FSI (Box 73)
      LRC #: HG 15.3
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-15069; FSI (Box 73)
      LRC #: HG 16.1
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-15070; FSI (Box 73)
      LRC #: HG 16.2
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-15071; FSI (Box 73)
      LRC #: HG 16.3
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-15072; FSI (Box 73)
      LRC #: HG 17.1
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-15073; FSI (Box 73)
      LRC #: HG 17.2
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-15074; FSI (Box 73)
      LRC #: HG 17.3
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-15075; FSI (Box 73)
      LRC #: HG 18.1
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-15076; FSI (Box 73)
      LRC #: HG 18.2
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-15077; FSI (Box 73)
      LRC #: HG 18.3
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-15078; FSI (Box 73)
      LRC #: HG 19.1
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-15079; FSI (Box 73)
      LRC #: HG 19.2
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-15080; FSI (Box 73)
      LRC #: HG 19.3
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-15081; FSI (Box 73)
      LRC #: HG 20.1
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-15082; FSI (Box 73)
      LRC #: HG 20.2
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-15083; FSI (Box 73)
      LRC #: HG 20.3
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-15084; FSI (Box 73)
      LRC #: HG 21.1
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-15085; FSI (Box 73)
      LRC #: HG 21.2
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-15086; FSI (Box 74)
      LRC #: HG 21.3
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-15087; FSI (Box 74)
      LRC #: HG 21.4
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-15088; FSI (Box 74)
      LRC #: HG 22.1
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-15089; FSI (Box 74)
      LRC #: HG 22.2
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-15090; FSI (Box 74)
      LRC #: HG 22.3
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-15091; FSI (Box 74)
      LRC #: HG 22.4
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-15092; FSI (Box 74)
      LRC #: HG 22.5
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-15093; FSI (Box 74)
      LRC #: HG 23.1
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-15094; FSI (Box 74)
      LRC #: HG 23.2
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-15095; FSI (Box 74)
      LRC #: HG 23.3
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-15096; FSI (Box 74)
      LRC #: HG 23.4
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-15097; FSI (Box 74)
      LRC #: HG 23.5
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-15098; FSI (Box 74)
      LRC #: HG 24.1
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-15099; FSI (Box 74)
      LRC #: HG 24.2
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-15100; FSI (Box 74)
      LRC #: HG 24.3
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-15101; FSI (Box 74)
      LRC #: HG 24.4
    - Hungarian, 1981; TR-15102 (Box 74)
      LRC #: HGK 1
    - Hungarian, 1981; TR-15103 (Box 74)
      LRC #: HGK 2
    - Hungarian, 1981; TR-15104 (Box 74)
      LRC #: HGK 3
    - Hungarian, 1981; TR-15105 (Box 74)
      LRC #: HGK 4
    - Hungarian, 1981; TR-15106 (Box 74)
      LRC #: HGK 5
    - Hungarian Text and Grammar, 1979; TR-15107; Wojatsek, C.; Playette Corp. (Box 74)
      LRC #: HGM 1-2
    - Hungarian Text and Grammar, 1979; TR-15108; Wojatsek, C.; Playette Corp. (Box 74)
    - Hungarian Text and Grammar, 1979; TR-15109; Wojatsek, C.; Playette Corp. (Box 74)
    - Intermediate Cambodian, Undated; TR-15110 (Box 74)
      LRC #: CBI 31
    - Intermediate Cambodian, Undated; TR-15111 (Box 74)
      LRC #: CBI 32
    - Intermediate Cambodian, Undated; TR-15112 (Box 74)
      LRC #: CBI 33
    - Intermediate Cambodian, Undated; TR-15113 (Box 74)
      LRC #: CBI 34
    - Intermediate Cambodian, Undated; TR-15114 (Box 74)
      LRC #: CBI 35
    - Intermediate Cambodian, Undated; TR-15115 (Box 74)
      LRC #: CBI 36
    - Intermediate Cambodian, Undated; TR-15116 (Box 74)
      LRC #: CBI 37
    - Intermediate Cambodian, Undated; TR-15117 (Box 74)
      LRC #: CBI 38
    - Intermediate Cambodian, Undated; TR-15118 (Box 74)
      LRC #: CBI 39
    - Intermediate Cambodian, Undated; TR-15119 (Box 74)
      LRC #: CBI 40
    - Intermediate Cambodian, Undated; TR-15120 (Box 74)
      LRC #: CBI 41
    - Intermediate Cambodian, Undated; TR-15121 (Box 74)
      LRC #: CBI 42
    - Intermediate Cambodian, Undated; TR-15122 (Box 74)
      LRC #: CBI 43
    - Intermediate Cambodian, Undated; TR-15123 (Box 74)
      LRC #: CBI 44
    - Intermediate Cambodian, Undated; TR-15124 (Box 74)
      LRC #: CBI 45
    - Intermediate Cambodian, Undated; TR-15125 (Box 74)
      LRC #: CBI 46
    - Intermediate Cambodian, Undated; TR-15126 (Box 74)
      LRC #: CBI 47
    - Intermediate Cambodian, Undated; TR-15127 (Box 74)
      LRC #: CBI 48
    - Intermediate Cambodian, Undated; TR-15128 (Box 74)
      LRC #: CBI 49
    - Intermediate Cambodian, Undated; TR-15129 (Box 74)
      LRC #: CBI 50
    - Modern Spoken Cambodian, Undated; TR-15130; Huffman (Box 75)
      LRC #: CB 1
    - Modern Spoken Cambodian, Undated; TR-15131; Huffman (Box 75)
      LRC #: CB 2
    - Modern Spoken Cambodian, Undated; TR-15132; Huffman (Box 75)
      LRC #: CB 3
    - Modern Spoken Cambodian, Undated; TR-15133; Huffman (Box 75)
      LRC #: CB 4
    - Modern Spoken Cambodian, Undated; TR-15134; Huffman (Box 75)
      LRC #: CB 5
    - Modern Spoken Cambodian, Undated; TR-15135; Huffman (Box 75)
      LRC #: CB 6
    - Modern Spoken Cambodian, Undated; TR-15136; Huffman (Box 75)
      LRC #: CB 7
    - Modern Spoken Cambodian, Undated; TR-15137; Huffman (Box 75)
      LRC #: CB 8
    - Modern Spoken Cambodian, Undated; TR-15138; Huffman (Box 75)
      LRC #: CB 9
    - Modern Spoken Cambodian, Undated; TR-15139; Huffman (Box 75)
      LRC #: CB 10
    - Modern Spoken Cambodian, Undated; TR-15140; Huffman (Box 75)
      LRC #: CB 11
    - Modern Spoken Cambodian, Undated; TR-15141; Huffman (Box 75)
      LRC #: CB 12
    - Modern Spoken Cambodian, Undated; TR-15142; Huffman (Box 75)
      LRC #: CB 13
    - Modern Spoken Cambodian, Undated; TR-15143; Huffman (Box 75)
      LRC #: CB 14
    - Modern Spoken Cambodian, Undated; TR-15144; Huffman (Box 75)
      LRC #: CB 15
    - Modern Spoken Cambodian, Undated; TR-15145; Huffman (Box 75)
      LRC #: CB 16
    - Modern Spoken Cambodian, Undated; TR-15146; Huffman (Box 75)
      LRC #: CB 17
    - Modern Spoken Cambodian, Undated; TR-15147; Huffman (Box 75)
      LRC #: CB 18
    - Modern Spoken Cambodian, Undated; TR-15148; Huffman (Box 75)
      LRC #: CB 19
    - Modern Spoken Cambodian, Undated; TR-15149; Huffman (Box 75)
      LRC #: CB 20
    - Modern Spoken Cambodian, Undated; TR-15150; Huffman (Box 75)
      LRC #: CB 21
    - Modern Spoken Cambodian, Undated; TR-15151; Huffman (Box 75)
      LRC #: CB 22
    - Modern Spoken Cambodian, Undated; TR-15152; Huffman (Box 75)
      LRC #: CB 23
    - Modern Spoken Cambodian, Undated; TR-15153; Huffman (Box 75)
      LRC #: CB 24
    - Modern Spoken Cambodian, Undated; TR-15154; Huffman (Box 75)
      LRC #: CB 25
    - Modern Spoken Cambodian, Undated; TR-15155; Huffman (Box 75)
      LRC #: CB 26
    - Modern Spoken Cambodian, Undated; TR-15156; Huffman (Box 75)
      LRC #: CB 27
    - Modern Spoken Cambodian, Undated; TR-15157; Huffman (Box 75)
      LRC #: CB 28
    - Modern Spoken Cambodian, Undated; TR-15158; Huffman (Box 75)
      LRC #: CB 29
    - Modern Spoken Cambodian, Undated; TR-15159; Huffman (Box 75)
      LRC #: CB 30
    - Modern Spoken Cambodian, Undated; TR-15160; Huffman (Box 75)
      LRC #: CB 31
    - Modern Spoken Cambodian, Undated; TR-15161; Huffman (Box 75)
      LRC #: CB 32
    - Modern Spoken Cambodian, Undated; TR-15162; Huffman (Box 75)
      LRC #: CB 33
    - Modern Spoken Cambodian, Undated; TR-15163; Huffman (Box 75)
      LRC #: CB 34
    - Modern Spoken Cambodian, Undated; TR-15164; Huffman (Box 75)
      LRC #: CB 35
    - Modern Spoken Cambodian, Undated; TR-15165; Huffman (Box 75)
      LRC #: CB 36
    - Modern Spoken Cambodian, Undated; TR-15166; Huffman (Box 75)
      LRC #: CB 37
    - Modern Spoken Cambodian, Undated; TR-15167; Huffman (Box 75)
      LRC #: CB 38
    - Modern Spoken Cambodian, Undated; TR-15168; Huffman (Box 75)
      LRC #: CB 39
    - Modern Spoken Cambodian, Undated; TR-15169; Huffman (Box 75)
      LRC #: CB 40
    - Modern Spoken Cambodian, Undated; TR-15170; Huffman (Box 75)
      LRC #: CB 41
    - Modern Spoken Cambodian, Undated; TR-15171; Huffman (Box 75)
      LRC #: CB 42
    - Modern Spoken Cambodian, Undated; TR-15172; Huffman (Box 76)
      LRC #: CB 43
    - Modern Spoken Cambodian, Undated; TR-15173; Huffman (Box 76)
      LRC #: CB 44
    - Modern Spoken Cambodian, Undated; TR-15174; Huffman (Box 76)
      LRC #: CB 45
    - Modern Spoken Cambodian, Undated; TR-15175; Huffman (Box 76)
      LRC #: CB 46
    - Modern Spoken Cambodian, Undated; TR-15176; Huffman (Box 76)
      LRC #: CB 47
    - Modern Spoken Cambodian, Undated; TR-15177; Huffman (Box 76)
      LRC #: CB 48
    - Modern Spoken Cambodian, Undated; TR-15178; Huffman (Box 76)
      LRC #: CB 49
    - Modern Spoken Cambodian, Undated; TR-15179; Huffman (Box 76)
      LRC #: CB 50
    - Modern Spoken Cambodian, Undated; TR-15180; Huffman (Box 76)
      LRC #: CB 51
    - Modern Spoken Cambodian, Undated; TR-15181; Huffman (Box 76)
      LRC #: CB 52
    - Modern Spoken Cambodian, Undated; TR-15182; Huffman (Box 76)
      LRC #: CB 53
    - Modern Spoken Cambodian, Undated; TR-15183; Huffman (Box 76)
      LRC #: CB 54
    - Intermediate Cambodian, Undated; TR-15184 (Box 76)
      LRC #: CBI 1
    - Intermediate Cambodian, Undated; TR-15185 (Box 76)
      LRC #: CBI 2
    - Intermediate Cambodian, Undated; TR-15186 (Box 76)
      LRC #: CBI 3
    - Intermediate Cambodian, Undated; TR-15187 (Box 76)
      LRC #: CBI 4
    - Intermediate Cambodian, Undated; TR-15188 (Box 76)
      LRC #: CBI 5
    - Intermediate Cambodian, Undated; TR-15189 (Box 76)
      LRC #: CBI 6
    - Intermediate Cambodian, Undated; TR-15190 (Box 76)
      LRC #: CBI 7
    - Intermediate Cambodian, Undated; TR-15191 (Box 76)
      LRC #: CBI 8
    - Intermediate Cambodian, Undated; TR-15192 (Box 76)
      LRC #: CBI 9
    - Intermediate Cambodian, Undated; TR-15193 (Box 76)
      LRC #: CBI 10
    - Intermediate Cambodian, Undated; TR-15194 (Box 76)
      LRC #: CBI 11
    - Intermediate Cambodian, Undated; TR-15195 (Box 76)
      LRC #: CBI 12
    - Intermediate Cambodian, Undated; TR-15196 (Box 76)
      LRC #: CBI 13
    - Intermediate Cambodian, Undated; TR-15197 (Box 76)
      LRC #: CBI 14
    - Intermediate Cambodian, Undated; TR-15198 (Box 76)
      LRC #: CBI 15
    - Intermediate Cambodian, Undated; TR-15199 (Box 76)
      LRC #: CBI 16
    - Intermediate Cambodian, Undated; TR-15200 (Box 76)
      LRC #: CBI 17
    - Intermediate Cambodian, Undated; TR-15201 (Box 76)
      LRC #: CBI 18
    - Intermediate Cambodian, Undated; TR-15202 (Box 76)
      LRC #: CBI 19
    - Intermediate Cambodian, Undated; TR-15203 (Box 76)
      LRC #: CBI 20
    - Intermediate Cambodian, Undated; TR-15204 (Box 76)
      LRC #: CBI 21
    - Intermediate Cambodian, Undated; TR-15205 (Box 76)
      LRC #: CBI 22
    - Intermediate Cambodian, Undated; TR-15206 (Box 76)
      LRC #: CBI 23
    - Intermediate Cambodian, Undated; TR-15207 (Box 76)
      LRC #: CBI 24
    - Intermediate Cambodian, Undated; TR-15208 (Box 76)
      LRC #: CBI 25
    - Intermediate Cambodian, Undated; TR-15209 (Box 76)
      LRC #: CBI 26
    - Intermediate Cambodian, Undated; TR-15210 (Box 76)
      LRC #: CBI 27
    - Intermediate Cambodian, Undated; TR-15211 (Box 76)
      LRC #: CBI 28
    - Intermediate Cambodian, Undated; TR-15212 (Box 76)
      LRC #: CBI 29
    - Intermediate Cambodian, Undated; TR-15213 (Box 76)
      LRC #: CBI 30
    - Greek Basic Course, 1967; TR-15214; FSI (Box 77)
      LRC #: G 1
    - Greek Basic Course, 1967; TR-15215; FSI (Box 77)
      LRC #: G 2
    - Greek Basic Course, 1967; TR-15216; FSI (Box 77)
      LRC #: G 3
    - Greek Basic Course, 1967; TR-15217; FSI (Box 77)
      LRC #: G 4
    - Greek Basic Course, 1967; TR-15218; FSI (Box 77)
      LRC #: G 5
    - Greek Basic Course, 1967; TR-15219; FSI (Box 77)
      LRC #: G 6
    - Greek Basic Course, 1967; TR-15220; FSI (Box 77)
      LRC #: G 7
    - Greek Basic Course, 1967; TR-15221; FSI (Box 77)
      LRC #: G 8
    - Greek Basic Course, 1967; TR-15222; FSI (Box 77)
      LRC #: G 9
    - Greek Basic Course, 1967; TR-15223; FSI (Box 77)
      LRC #: G 10
    - Greek Basic Course, 1967; TR-15224; FSI (Box 77)
      LRC #: G 11
    - Greek Basic Course, 1967; TR-15225; FSI (Box 77)
      LRC #: G 12
    - Greek Basic Course, 1967; TR-15226; FSI (Box 77)
      LRC #: G 13
    - Greek Basic Course, 1967; TR-15227; FSI (Box 77)
      LRC #: G 14
    - Greek Basic Course, 1967; TR-15228; FSI (Box 77)
      LRC #: G 15
    - Greek Basic Course, 1967; TR-15229; FSI (Box 77)
      LRC #: G 16
    - Greek Basic Course, 1967; TR-15230; FSI (Box 77)
      LRC #: G 17
    - Greek Basic Course, 1967; TR-15231; FSI (Box 77)
      LRC #: G 18
    - Greek Basic Course, 1967; TR-15232; FSI (Box 77)
      LRC #: G 19
    - Greek Basic Course, 1967; TR-15233; FSI (Box 77)
      LRC #: G 20
    - Greek Basic Course, 1967; TR-15234; FSI (Box 77)
      LRC #: G 21
    - Greek Basic Course, 1967; TR-15235; FSI (Box 77)
      LRC #: G 22
    - Greek Basic Course, 1967; TR-15236; FSI (Box 77)
      LRC #: G 23
    - Greek Basic Course, 1967; TR-15237; FSI (Box 77)
      LRC #: G 24.1
    - Greek Basic Course, 1967; TR-15238; FSI (Box 77)
      LRC #: G 24.2
    - Greek Basic Course, 1967; TR-15239; FSI (Box 77)
      LRC #: G 25.1
    - Greek Basic Course, 1967; TR-15240; FSI (Box 77)
      LRC #: G 25.2
    - Greek Basic Course, 1967; TR-15241; FSI (Box 77)
      LRC #: G 26.1
    - Greek Basic Course, 1967; TR-15242; FSI (Box 77)
      LRC #: G 26.2
    - Greek Basic Course, 1967; TR-15243; FSI (Box 77)
      LRC #: G 27
    - Greek Basic Course, 1967; TR-15244; FSI (Box 77)
      LRC #: G 28.1
    - Greek Basic Course, 1967; TR-15245; FSI (Box 77)
      LRC #: G 28.2
    - Greek Basic Course, 1967; TR-15246; FSI (Box 77)
      LRC #: G 29
    - Greek Basic Course, 1967; TR-15247; FSI (Box 77)
      LRC #: G 30
    - Greek Basic Course, 1967; TR-15248; FSI (Box 77)
      LRC #: G 31.1
    - Greek Basic Course, 1967; TR-15249; FSI (Box 77)
      LRC #: G 31.2
    - Greek Basic Course, 1967; TR-15250; FSI (Box 77)
      LRC #: G 32
    - Greek Basic Course, 1967; TR-15251; FSI (Box 77)
      LRC #: G 33.1
    - Greek Basic Course, 1967; TR-15252; FSI (Box 77)
      LRC #: G 33.2
    - Greek Basic Course, 1967; TR-15253; FSI (Box 77)
      LRC #: G 34
    - Greek Basic Course, 1967; TR-15254; FSI (Box 77)
      LRC #: G 35.1
    - Greek Basic Course, 1967; TR-15255; FSI (Box 77)
      LRC #: G 35.2
    - Greek Basic Course, 1967; TR-15256; FSI (Box 77)
      LRC #: G 36
    - Greek Basic Course, 1967; TR-15257; FSI (Box 77)
      LRC #: G 37
    - Greek Basic Course, 1967; TR-15258; FSI (Box 77)
      LRC #: G 38
    - Greek Basic Course, 1967; TR-15259; FSI (Box 77)
      LRC #: G 39
    - Greek Basic Course, 1967; TR-15260; FSI (Box 77)
      LRC #: G 40
    - Greek Basic Course, 1967; TR-15261; FSI (Box 77)
      LRC #: G 41
    - Greek Basic Course, 1967; TR-15262; FSI (Box 77)
      LRC #: G 42
    - Greek Basic Course, 1967; TR-15263; FSI (Box 77)
      LRC #: G 43
    - Greek Basic Course, 1967; TR-15264; FSI (Box 78)
      LRC #: G 44
    - Greek Basic Course, 1967; TR-15265; FSI (Box 78)
      LRC #: G 45
    - Greek Basic Course, 1967; TR-15266; FSI (Box 78)
      LRC #: G 46
    - Greek Basic Course, 1967; TR-15267; FSI (Box 78)
      LRC #: G 47
    - Greek Basic Course, 1967; TR-15268; FSI (Box 78)
      LRC #: G 48
    - Greek Basic Course, 1967; TR-15269; FSI (Box 78)
      LRC #: G 49
    - Greek, Undated; TR-15270; FSI (Box 78)
      LRC #: G 50
    - Greek, Undated; TR-15271; FSI (Box 78)
      LRC #: G 51
    - Greek, Undated; TR-15272; FSI (Box 78)
      LRC #: G 52
    - Greek, Undated; TR-15273; FSI (Box 78)
      LRC #: G 53
    - Greek, Undated; TR-15274; FSI (Box 78)
      LRC #: G 54
    - Greek, Undated; TR-15275; FSI (Box 78)
      LRC #: G 55
    - Greek, Undated; TR-15276; FSI (Box 78)
      LRC #: G 56-58
    - Greek, Undated; TR-15277; FSI (Box 78)
      LRC #: G 59-62
    - Greek, Undated; TR-15278; FSI (Box 78)
      LRC #: G 63-66
    - Greek, Undated; TR-15279; FSI (Box 78)
      LRC #: G 67-70
    - Greek, Undated; TR-15280; FSI (Box 78)
      LRC #: G 71-74
    - Greek, Undated; TR-15281; FSI (Box 78)
      LRC #: G 75-75A
    - Greek Review, Undated; TR-15282; FSI (Box 78)
      LRC #: GX 1
    - Greek Review, Undated; TR-15283; FSI (Box 78)
      LRC #: GX 2
    - Greek Review, Undated; TR-15284; FSI (Box 78)
      LRC #: GX 3
    - Greek Review, Undated; TR-15285; FSI (Box 78)
      LRC #: GX 4
    - Greek Review, Undated; TR-15286; FSI (Box 78)
      LRC #: GX 5
    - Greek Review, Undated; TR-15287; FSI (Box 78)
      LRC #: GX 6
    - Greek Review, Undated; TR-15288; FSI (Box 78)
      LRC #: GX 7
    - Greek Review, Undated; TR-15289; FSI (Box 78)
      LRC #: GX 8
    - Greek Review, Undated; TR-15290; FSI (Box 78)
      LRC #: GX 9
    - Greek Review, Undated; TR-15291; FSI (Box 78)
      LRC #: GX 10
    - Greek Review, Undated; TR-15292; FSI (Box 78)
      LRC #: GX 11
    - Greek Review, Undated; TR-15293; FSI (Box 78)
      LRC #: GX 12
    - Greek Review, Undated; TR-15294; FSI (Box 78)
      LRC #: GX 13
    - Greek Review, Undated; TR-15295; FSI (Box 78)
      LRC #: GX 14
    - Greek Review, Undated; TR-15296; FSI (Box 78)
      LRC #: GX 15
    - Greek Review, Undated; TR-15297; FSI (Box 78)
      LRC #: GX 16
    - Greek Review, Undated; TR-15298; FSI (Box 78)
      LRC #: GX 17
    - Greek Review, Undated; TR-15299; FSI (Box 78)
      LRC #: GX 18
    - Greek Review, Undated; TR-15300; FSI (Box 78)
    - Greek Review, Undated; TR-15301; FSI (Box 78)